<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="es-ES">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> namespace contains classes that support and handle channels and channel sinks, which are used as the transport medium when a client calls a method on a remote object.</source>
          <target state="translated">El espacio de nombres <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> contiene clases que admiten y controlan los canales y los receptores de canales, que se utilizan como el medio de transporte cuando un cliente llama a un método en un objeto remoto.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels are objects that transport messages between applications across remoting boundaries, whether between application domains, processes, or computers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Los canales son objetos que transportan los mensajes entre las aplicaciones a través de límites remotos, por ejemplo, dominios de aplicación, procesos y equipos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>A channel can listen on an endpoint for inbound messages, send outbound messages to another endpoint, or both.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un canal puede escuchar los mensajes entrantes en un punto de conexión, enviar los mensajes salientes a otro punto de conexión o ambas cosas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This enables you to plug in a wide range of protocols, even if the common language runtime is not at the other end of the channel.</source>
          <target state="translated">Esto permite conectar una gran variedad de protocolos, incluso si Common Language Runtime no está en el otro extremo del canal.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels send each object along a chain of channel sink objects prior to sending or after receiving a message.</source>
          <target state="translated">Los canales envían cada objeto a lo largo de una cadena de objetos de receptores de canal antes de enviar o después de recibir un mensaje.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This sink chain contains sinks required for basic channel functionality, such as transport or stack builder sinks, but you can customize the channel sink chain to perform special tasks with a message or a stream.</source>
          <target state="translated">Esta cadena de receptores contiene los receptores necesarios para la funcionalidad básica del canal, como receptores de generador de pila o de transporte, pero puede personalizar la cadena de receptores de canal para llevar a cabo tareas especiales con un mensaje o una secuencia.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Each sink in each chain receives the object, performs a specific operation, and passes it on to the next sink in the chain.</source>
          <target state="translated">Cada receptor de cada cadena recibe el objeto, realiza una operación concreta y lo pasa al siguiente receptor de la cadena.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>There is no rule that the exact object received by a message sink must be passed on to the next sink, though this will often be the case.</source>
          <target state="translated">No hay ninguna regla que se debe pasar el objeto exacto recibido por un receptor de mensajes el siguiente receptor, aunque suele ser el caso.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>For more information, see <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>Channels<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> and <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>Sinks and Sink Chains<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Para obtener más información, consulte <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>canales<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> y <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>receptores y cadenas de receptores<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>