<Type Name="PerformanceCounterCategory" FullName="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="f9fd67ab410cfdb0ca2f5254530cabe162bde154" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="5a49536d99d2d0b54e4cb7280870903e043272df" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="es-ES" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="07/03/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="37663817" />
  </Metadata>
  <TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public sealed class PerformanceCounterCategory" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi sealed beforefieldinit PerformanceCounterCategory extends System.Object" />
  <TypeSignature Language="DocId" Value="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" />
  <TypeSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public NotInheritable Class PerformanceCounterCategory" />
  <TypeSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public ref class PerformanceCounterCategory sealed" />
  <TypeSignature Language="F#" Value="type PerformanceCounterCategory = class" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>System.Object</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces />
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="4f675-101">Represents a performance object, which defines a category of performance counters.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="4f675-101">Represents a performance object, which defines a category of performance counters.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!IMPORTANT]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-102">Creación o eliminación de un contador de rendimiento requiere la sincronización del código subyacente mediante el uso de una exclusión mutua con nombre.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-102">Creating or deleting a performance counter requires synchronization of the underlying code by using a named mutex.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-103">Si una aplicación con muchos privilegios bloquea la exclusión mutua con nombre, intenta crear o eliminar un contador de rendimiento hace que la aplicación deje de responder hasta que se libere el bloqueo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-103">If a highly privileged application locks the named mutex, attempts to create or delete a performance counter causes the application to stop responding until the lock is released.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-104">Para evitar este problema, no conceder nunca <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityPermissionFlag.UnmanagedCode> permiso al código de confianza.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-104">To help avoid this problem, never grant <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityPermissionFlag.UnmanagedCode> permission to untrusted code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-105">Además, <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityPermissionFlag.UnmanagedCode> permiso potencialmente permite omitir otros permisos y solo debe concederse al código de plena confianza.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-105">In addition, <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityPermissionFlag.UnmanagedCode> permission potentially allows other permissions to be bypassed and should only be granted to highly trusted code.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-106">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> la instancia <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> propiedad se muestra en el campo de objeto de rendimiento del cuadro de diálogo Agregar contadores de la aplicación Visor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-106">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> instance's <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> property is displayed in the Performance Object field of the Performance Viewer application's Add Counter dialog box.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-107">La <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> clase proporciona varios métodos para interactuar con contadores y categorías en el equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-107">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> class provides several methods for interacting with counters and categories on the computer.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-108">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> métodos le permiten definir categorías personalizadas.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-108">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> methods enable you to define custom categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-109">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> método proporciona una manera de quitar las categorías del equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-109">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> method provides a way to remove categories from the computer.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-110">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> método le permite ver la lista de categorías, mientras que <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A> recupera todos los datos de contador e instancia de asociada con una única categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-110">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> method enables you to view the list of categories, while <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A> retrieves all the counter and instance data associated with a single category.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-111">Un contador de rendimiento publica los datos de rendimiento acerca de una aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-111">A performance counter publishes performance data about an application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-112">Las categorías incluyen los componentes físicos (como procesadores, discos y memoria) y los objetos del sistema (por ejemplo, procesos y subprocesos).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-112">Categories include physical components (such as processors, disks, and memory) and system objects (such as processes and threads).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-113">Contadores del sistema que están relacionados con el mismo objeto de rendimiento se agrupan en una categoría que indica su enfoque común.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-113">System counters that are related to the same performance object are grouped into a category that indicates their common focus.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-114">Cuando se crea una instancia de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> (clase), primero debe indicarse la categoría con el que interactuará el componente y, a continuación, elija un contador de dicha categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-114">When you create an instance of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class, you first indicate the category with which the component will interact, and then you choose a counter from that category.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-115">Por ejemplo, una categoría de contador de Windows es la categoría de memoria.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-115">For example, one Windows counter category is the Memory category.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-116">Contadores del sistema de esta categoría de seguimiento de los datos de memoria como el número de bytes disponibles y el número de bytes almacenados en caché.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-116">System counters within this category track memory data such as the number of bytes available and the number of bytes cached.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-117">Si desea trabajar con los bytes almacenados en caché en la aplicación, debe crear una instancia de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> componente, conectarla a la categoría de memoria y, a continuación, elegir el contador adecuado (en este caso, los Bytes almacenados en caché) de esa categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-117">If you wanted to work with the bytes cached in your application, you would create an instance of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> component, connect it to the Memory category, and then pick the appropriate counter (in this case, Cached Bytes) from that category.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-118">Aunque el sistema realiza muchas más categorías de contador disponibles, las categorías que probablemente interactuará con más frecuencia son las categorías de la memoria caché, memoria, objetos, DiscoFísico, proceso, procesador, servidor, del sistema y subproceso.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-118">Although your system makes many more counter categories available, the categories that you will probably interact with most frequently are the Cache, Memory, Objects, PhysicalDisk, Process, Processor, Server, System, and Thread categories.</span></span>  
  
> [!IMPORTANT]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-119">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.RemoveInstance%2A> método en el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> clase lanzará el contador y, si se selecciona la opción de volver a utilizar para esa categoría, se volverá a la instancia del contador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-119">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.RemoveInstance%2A> method in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class will release the counter and, if the reuse option is selected for that category, the instance of the counter will be reused.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-120">Esto podría causar una condición de carrera si otro proceso o incluso otra parte del código está intentando escribir en la instancia del contador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-120">This could cause a race condition if another process or even another part of the code is trying to write to the counter instance.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-121">Se recomienda encarecidamente que se crean nuevas categorías de contador de rendimiento durante la instalación de la aplicación, no durante la ejecución de la aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-121">It is strongly recommended that new performance counter categories be created during the installation of the application, not during the execution of the application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-122">Esto permite que el tiempo para el sistema operativo actualizar su lista de categorías de contador de rendimiento registrados.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-122">This allows time for the operating system to refresh its list of registered performance counter categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-123">Si no se ha actualizado la lista, se producirá un error al intentar utilizar la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-123">If the list has not been refreshed, the attempt to use the category will fail.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-124">Categorías de contador de rendimiento instaladas con el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] usar memoria compartida independiente, con cada categoría de contador de rendimiento tiene su propia memoria.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-124">Performance counter categories installed with the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] use separate shared memory, with each performance counter category having its own memory.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-125">Puede especificar el tamaño de memoria compartida independiente mediante la creación de un valor DWORD denominado FileMappingSize en la clave del Registro HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<nombre de categoría >* \ Rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-125">You can specify the size of separate shared memory by creating a DWORD named FileMappingSize in the registry key HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<category name>* \Performance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-126">El valor de FileMappingSize se establece en el tamaño de memoria compartida de la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-126">The FileMappingSize value is set to the shared memory size of the category.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-127">El tamaño predeterminado es decimal 131072.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-127">The default size is 131072 decimal.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-128">Si el valor de FileMappingSize no está presente, el `fileMappingSize` valor del atributo para el `performanceCounters` se utiliza el elemento especificado en el archivo Machine.config, provocando una sobrecarga adicional para el procesamiento del archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-128">If the FileMappingSize value is not present, the `fileMappingSize` attribute value for the `performanceCounters` element specified in the Machine.config file is used, causing additional overhead for configuration file processing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-129">Puede apreciar una mejora del rendimiento de inicio de la aplicación estableciendo el tamaño de asignación de archivo en el registro.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-129">You can realize a performance improvement for application startup by setting the file mapping size in the registry.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-130">Para obtener más información sobre el tamaño de asignación de archivo, consulte [ &lt;performanceCounters&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/trace-debug/performancecounters-element.md).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-130">For more information about the file mapping size, see [&lt;performanceCounters&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/trace-debug/performancecounters-element.md).</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-131">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> y su <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> existe en el equipo local o en otro equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-131">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> and its <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> exist on the local computer or on another computer.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-132">Si estos objetos no existen en el equipo local, en el ejemplo, opcionalmente, crearlos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-132">If these objects do not exist on the local computer, the example optionally creates them.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-133">Usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> método para determinar si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> existe.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-133">It uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> method to determine whether the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> exists.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-134">Si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> no existe y se especifica ningún nombre de contador o si el equipo es un equipo remoto, se cierra el ejemplo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-134">If the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> does not exist and no counter name is specified, or if the computer is a remote machine, the example exits.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-135">Si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> se proporciona el nombre, el ejemplo se usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> método y muestra el resultado al usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-135">If a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> name is provided, the example uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> method and displays the result to the user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-136">Si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> no existe, el usuario puede eliminar y volver a crear la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el nuevo <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-136">If the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> does not exist, the user can delete and re-create the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the new <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-137">Si lo hace, la categoría se elimina mediante el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-137">If the user does so, the category is deleted using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-138">Si se solicita, en el ejemplo se crea ahora el nuevo <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> utilizando el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-138">If requested, the example now creates the new <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-139">Si se especifica un nombre de instancia, el ejemplo se usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> método y muestra el resultado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-139">If an instance name is specified, the example uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> method and displays the result.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Class#27](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Class/CS/perfcountercatcreateexist.cs#27)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Class#27](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Class/VB/perfcountercatcreateexist.vb#27)]  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
    <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
    <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterSample" />
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <MemberGroup MemberName=".ctor">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-140">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-140">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PerformanceCounterCategory ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.#ctor" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; PerformanceCounterCategory();" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-141">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class, leaves the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property empty, and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> property to the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-141">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class, leaves the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property empty, and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> property to the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-142">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> propiedad debe establecerse antes de asociar esta <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> instancia con un objeto de rendimiento en el servidor.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-142">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> property must be set before associating this <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> instance with a performance object on the server.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-143">De lo contrario, se inicia una excepción.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-143">Otherwise, an exception is thrown.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-144">El ejemplo de código siguiente acepta una <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> nombre y un nombre de equipo desde la línea de comandos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-144">The following code example accepts a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> name and a computer name from the command line.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-145">Crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> mediante la sobrecarga del constructor adecuada para el número de parámetros proporcionados, a continuación, se muestran sus propiedades.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-145">It creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> using the constructor overload appropriate for the number of parameters provided, then displays its properties.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfcountercatctor.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatctor.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-146">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-146">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-147">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-147">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PerformanceCounterCategory (string categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor(string categoryName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.#ctor(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New (categoryName As String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; PerformanceCounterCategory(System::String ^ categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="new System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory : string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="new System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory categoryName" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-148">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which to associate this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-148">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which to associate this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-149">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class, sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property to the specified value, and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> property to the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-149">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class, sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property to the specified value, and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> property to the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-150">El ejemplo de código siguiente acepta una <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> nombre y un nombre de equipo desde la línea de comandos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-150">The following code example accepts a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> name and a computer name from the command line.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-151">Crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> mediante la sobrecarga del constructor que sea adecuada para el número de parámetros proporcionados, a continuación, se muestran sus propiedades.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-151">It creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> using the constructor overload that is appropriate for the number of parameters provided, then displays its properties.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfcountercatctor.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatctor.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-152">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-152">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-153">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-153">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-154">para leer información de categoría, como el nombre de categoría.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-154">for reading category information, such as the category name.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-155">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-155">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PerformanceCounterCategory (string categoryName, string machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor(string categoryName, string machineName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.#ctor(System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New (categoryName As String, machineName As String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; PerformanceCounterCategory(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="new System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory : string * string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="new System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory (categoryName, machineName)" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="machineName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-156">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which to associate this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-156">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which to associate this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="machineName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-157">The computer on which the performance counter category and its associated counters exist.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-157">The computer on which the performance counter category and its associated counters exist.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-158">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties to the specified values.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-158">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> class and sets the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties to the specified values.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-159">El ejemplo de código siguiente acepta una <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> nombre y un nombre de equipo desde la línea de comandos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-159">The following code example accepts a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> name and a computer name from the command line.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-160">Crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> mediante la sobrecarga del constructor que sea adecuada para el número de parámetros proporcionados, a continuación, se muestran sus propiedades.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-160">It creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> using the constructor overload that is appropriate for the number of parameters provided, then displays its properties.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfcountercatctor.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatctor.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-161">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-161">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-162">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> syntax is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-162">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> syntax is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-163">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-163">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-164">para leer la información de categoría, como el nombre de equipo y de categoría.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-164">for reading category information, such as the computer and category name.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-165">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-165">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CategoryHelp">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string CategoryHelp { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string CategoryHelp" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public ReadOnly Property CategoryHelp As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ CategoryHelp { System::String ^ get(); };" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.CategoryHelp : string" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-166">Gets the category's help text.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-166">Gets the category's help text.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-167">Una descripción del objeto de rendimiento que esta categoría mide.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-167">A description of the performance object that this category measures.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-168">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-168">The following code example creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-169">Pide al usuario el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y nombres de equipo, a continuación, Establece el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> propiedades de los valores introducidos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-169">It prompts the user for the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and computer names, then sets the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> properties from the entered values.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-170">A continuación, muestra los valores de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> propiedades o se muestra un mensaje de error si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> no es accesible.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-170">It then displays the values of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> properties, or it displays an error message if the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> cannot be accessed.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfCounterCatProps.cs#8)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatprops.vb#8)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-171">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-171">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-172">The category name must be set before getting the category help.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-172">The category name must be set before getting the category help.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-173">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-173">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.CounterHelp" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CategoryName">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string CategoryName { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string CategoryName" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property CategoryName As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ CategoryName { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.CategoryName : string with get, set" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-174">Gets or sets the name of the performance object that defines this category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-174">Gets or sets the name of the performance object that defines this category.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-175">El nombre de la categoría de contador de rendimiento u objeto de rendimiento, con la que se va a asociar este <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instancia.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-175">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which to associate this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-176">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-176">The following code example creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-177">Pide al usuario el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y nombres de equipo, a continuación, Establece el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> propiedades de los valores introducidos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-177">It prompts the user for the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and computer names, then sets the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> properties from the entered values.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-178">A continuación, muestra los valores de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> propiedades o se muestra un mensaje de error si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> no es accesible.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-178">It then displays the values of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> properties, or it displays an error message if the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> cannot be accessed.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfCounterCatProps.cs#8)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatprops.vb#8)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-179">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-179">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-180">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-180">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-181">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-181">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-182">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-182">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CategoryType">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType CategoryType { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType CategoryType" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryType" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public ReadOnly Property CategoryType As PerformanceCounterCategoryType" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategoryType CategoryType { System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategoryType get(); };" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.CategoryType : System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryType" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-183">Gets the performance counter category type.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-183">Gets the performance counter category type.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-184">Uno de los valores de <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-184">One of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" /> values.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-185">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryType%2A> propiedad indica si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto puede tener varias instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-185">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryType%2A> property indicates whether the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object can have multiple instances.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-186">Los valores posibles son <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.MultiInstance>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.SingleInstance>, o <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.Unknown>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-186">The possible values are <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.MultiInstance>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.SingleInstance>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.Unknown>.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-187">Hay dos tipos de categorías de contador de rendimiento: instancia única y varias instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-187">There are two types of performance counter categories: single-instance and multi-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-188">De forma predeterminada, una categoría es de instancia única cuando se crea y se convierte en varias instancias cuando se agrega otra instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-188">By default, a category is single-instance when it is created and becomes multi-instance when another instance is added.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-189">Las categorías se crean cuando se configura una aplicación, y se agregan instancias en tiempo de ejecución.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-189">Categories are created when an application is set up, and instances are added at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-190">En las versiones 1.0 y 1.1 de .NET Framework, no es necesario saber si una categoría de contador de rendimiento es de varias instancias o de instancia única.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-190">In the .NET Framework versions 1.0 and 1.1, it is not necessary to know if a performance counter category is multi-instance or single-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-191">En el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeración se utiliza para indicar si un contador de rendimiento puede tener varias instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-191">In the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeration is used to indicate whether a performance counter can have multiple instances.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="CounterExists">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-192">Determines whether a specified counter is registered to a particular category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-192">Determines whether a specified counter is registered to a particular category.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="CounterExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public bool CounterExists (string counterName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance bool CounterExists(string counterName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function CounterExists (counterName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; bool CounterExists(System::String ^ counterName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.CounterExists : string -&gt; bool" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.CounterExists counterName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="counterName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="counterName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-193">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-193">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-194">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to this category, which is indicated by the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-194">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to this category, which is indicated by the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-195">
            <see langword="true" /> if the counter is registered to the category that is specified by the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-195">
              <see langword="true" /> if the counter is registered to the category that is specified by the <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> and <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> properties; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-196">Debe establecer el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> propiedad antes de llamar a este método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-196">You must set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> property before calling this method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-197">De lo contrario, se inicia una excepción.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-197">Otherwise, an exception is thrown.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-198">Si no ha establecido la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> propiedad, este método utiliza el equipo local (".").</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-198">If you have not set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> property, this method uses the local computer (".").</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-199">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-199">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-200">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-200">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-201">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-201">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-202">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-202">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-203">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-203">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-204">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-204">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-205">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-205">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-206">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> existe.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-206">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-207">Obtiene un nombre de categoría, el nombre del contador y el nombre del equipo desde la línea de comandos, si se han proporcionado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-207">It gets a category name, counter name, and computer name from the command line, if they are given.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-208">Crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto mediante el correspondiente <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor%2A>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-208">It creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object using the appropriate <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor%2A>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-209">A continuación, usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%28System.String%29> método para determinar si especificado <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> existe y se informa al usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-209">It then uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%28System.String%29> method to determine whether the specified <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> exists, and informs the user.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcountercatobjexists.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatobjcountexists.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-210">The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-210">The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-211">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property has not been set.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-211">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property has not been set.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-212">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-212">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-213">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-213">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CounterExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool CounterExists (string counterName, string categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool CounterExists(string counterName, string categoryName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function CounterExists (counterName As String, categoryName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool CounterExists(System::String ^ counterName, System::String ^ categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member CounterExists : string * string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists (counterName, categoryName)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="counterName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="counterName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-214">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-214">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-215">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which the specified performance counter is associated.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-215">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which the specified performance counter is associated.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-216">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to the specified category on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-216">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to the specified category on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-217">
            <see langword="true" />, if the counter is registered to the specified category on the local computer; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-217">
              <see langword="true" />, if the counter is registered to the specified category on the local computer; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-218">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-218">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-219">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-219">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-220">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-220">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-221">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-221">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-222">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-222">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-223">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-223">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-224">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-224">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-225">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> existe.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-225">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-226">Obtiene un nombre de categoría, el nombre del contador y el nombre del equipo desde la línea de comandos, si se han proporcionado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-226">It gets a category name, counter name, and computer name from the command line, if they are given.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-227">Utilizan las sobrecargas estáticas de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> método para determinar si especificado <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> nombre existe en el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-227">It uses the static overloads of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> method to determine whether the specified <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> name exists in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-228">La sobrecarga se selecciona en función de si se proporciona un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-228">The overload is selected based on whether a computer name is provided.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcountercatstatcounterexists.cs#8)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatstatcountexists.vb#8)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-229">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-229">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-230">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-230">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-231">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-231">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-232">The category name does not exist.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-232">The category name does not exist.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-233">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-233">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-234">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-234">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-235">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-235">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-236">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-236">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CounterExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool CounterExists (string counterName, string categoryName, string machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool CounterExists(string counterName, string categoryName, string machineName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String,System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function CounterExists (counterName As String, categoryName As String, machineName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool CounterExists(System::String ^ counterName, System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member CounterExists : string * string * string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists (counterName, categoryName, machineName)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="counterName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="machineName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="counterName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-237">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-237">The name of the performance counter to look for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-238">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which the specified performance counter is associated.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-238">The name of the performance counter category, or performance object, with which the specified performance counter is associated.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="machineName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-239">The name of the computer on which the performance counter category and its associated counters exist.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-239">The name of the computer on which the performance counter category and its associated counters exist.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-240">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to the specified category on a remote computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-240">Determines whether the specified counter is registered to the specified category on a remote computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-241">
            <see langword="true" />, if the counter is registered to the specified category on the specified computer; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-241">
              <see langword="true" />, if the counter is registered to the specified category on the specified computer; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-242">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-242">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-243">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-243">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-244">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-244">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-245">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-245">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-246">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-246">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-247">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-247">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-248">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-248">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-249">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> existe.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-249">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-250">Obtiene un nombre de categoría, el nombre del contador y el nombre del equipo desde la línea de comandos, si se han proporcionado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-250">It gets a category name, counter name, and computer name from the command line, if they are given.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-251">Utilizan las sobrecargas estáticas de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> método para determinar si especificado <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> nombre existe en el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-251">It uses the static overloads of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists%2A> method to determine whether the specified <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> name exists in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-252">La sobrecarga se selecciona en función de si se proporciona un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-252">The overload is selected based on whether a computer name is provided.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcountercatstatcounterexists.cs#8)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatstatcountexists.vb#8)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-253">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-253">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-254">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-254">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-255">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-255">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-256">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-256">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-257">The category name does not exist.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-257">The category name does not exist.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-258">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-258">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-259">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-259">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-260">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-260">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-261">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-261">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="Create">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-262">Registers a custom performance counter category and one or more counters with the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-262">Registers a custom performance counter category and one or more counters with the system.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="Create">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create (string categoryName, string categoryHelp, System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection counterData);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create(string categoryName, string categoryHelp, class System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection counterData) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create(System.String,System.String,System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Create (categoryName As String, categoryHelp As String, counterData As CounterCreationDataCollection) As PerformanceCounterCategory" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^ Create(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ categoryHelp, System::Diagnostics::CounterCreationDataCollection ^ counterData);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Create : string * string * System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create (categoryName, categoryHelp, counterData)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.Obsolete("Use another overload that uses PerformanceCounterCategoryType instead")</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryHelp" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="counterData" Type="System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-263">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-263">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-264">A description of the custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-264">A description of the custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterData">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-265">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" /> that specifies the counters to create as part of the new category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-265">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" /> that specifies the counters to create as part of the new category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-266">Registers the custom performance counter category containing the specified counters on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-266">Registers the custom performance counter category containing the specified counters on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-267">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new custom category, or performance object.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-267">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new custom category, or performance object.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-268">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-268">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-269">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-269">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-270">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-270">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-271">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-271">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-272">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-272">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-273">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-273">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-274">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-274">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-275">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> existe el objeto denominado "orders".</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-275">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object named "orders" exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-276">Si no, crea el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto utilizando un <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> objeto que contiene dos contadores de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-276">If not, it creates the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object by using a <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> object that contains two performance counters.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CPP/ccd.cpp#1)]
 [!code-csharp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CS/ccd.cs#1)]
 [!code-vb[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/VB/ccd.vb#1)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-277">A counter name that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is <see langword="null" /> or an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-277">A counter name that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is <see langword="null" /> or an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-278">-or-  A counter that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection already exists.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-278">-or-  A counter that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection already exists.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-279">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> parameter has invalid syntax.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-279">-or-  The <paramref name="counterName" /> parameter has invalid syntax.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-280">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-280">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-281">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-281">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-282">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-282">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-283">-or-  The layout of the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is incorrect for base counters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-283">-or-  The layout of the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is incorrect for base counters.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-284">A counter of type <see langword="AverageCount64" />, <see langword="AverageTimer32" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimerInverse" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100Ns" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100NsInverse" />, <see langword="RawFraction" />, <see langword="SampleFraction" /> or <see langword="SampleCounter" /> has to be immediately followed by one of the base counter types (<see langword="AverageBase" />, <see langword="MultiBase" />, <see langword="RawBase" />, or <see langword="SampleBase" />).</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-284">A counter of type <see langword="AverageCount64" />, <see langword="AverageTimer32" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimerInverse" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100Ns" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100NsInverse" />, <see langword="RawFraction" />, <see langword="SampleFraction" /> or <see langword="SampleCounter" /> has to be immediately followed by one of the base counter types (<see langword="AverageBase" />, <see langword="MultiBase" />, <see langword="RawBase" />, or <see langword="SampleBase" />).</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-285">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-285">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-286">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-286">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-287">para realizar tareas administrativas en categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-287">for performing administrative tasks on performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-288">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-288">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Create">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create (string categoryName, string categoryHelp, System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection counterData);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create(string categoryName, string categoryHelp, valuetype System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, class System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection counterData) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create(System.String,System.String,System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType,System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Create (categoryName As String, categoryHelp As String, categoryType As PerformanceCounterCategoryType, counterData As CounterCreationDataCollection) As PerformanceCounterCategory" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^ Create(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ categoryHelp, System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, System::Diagnostics::CounterCreationDataCollection ^ counterData);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Create : string * string * System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType * System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create (categoryName, categoryHelp, categoryType, counterData)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryHelp" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryType" Type="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" />
        <Parameter Name="counterData" Type="System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-289">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-289">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-290">A description of the custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-290">A description of the custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryType">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-291">One of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" /> values.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-291">One of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" /> values.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterData">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-292">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" /> that specifies the counters to create as part of the new category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-292">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" /> that specifies the counters to create as part of the new category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-293">Registers the custom performance counter category containing the specified counters on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-293">Registers the custom performance counter category containing the specified counters on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-294">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new custom category, or performance object.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-294">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new custom category, or performance object.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-295">El `categoryType` parámetro especifica si la categoría de contador de rendimiento es de instancia única o instancias múltiples.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-295">The `categoryType` parameter specifies whether the performance counter category is single-instance or multi-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-296">De forma predeterminada, una categoría es de instancia única cuando se crea y se convierte en varias instancias cuando se agrega otra instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-296">By default, a category is single-instance when it is created and becomes multi-instance when another instance is added.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-297">Las categorías se crean cuando se configura una aplicación, y se agregan instancias en tiempo de ejecución.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-297">Categories are created when an application is set up, and instances are added at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-298">En las versiones 1.0 y 1.1 de .NET Framework, no es necesario saber si una categoría de contador de rendimiento es de varias instancias o de instancia única.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-298">In the  .NET Framework versions 1.0 and 1.1, it is not necessary to know if a performance counter category is multi-instance or single-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-299">En el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeración se utiliza para indicar si un contador de rendimiento puede tener varias instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-299">In the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeration is used to indicate whether a performance counter can have multiple instances.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-300">Categorías de contador de rendimiento instaladas con el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] usar memoria compartida independiente, con cada categoría de contador de rendimiento tiene su propia memoria.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-300">Performance counter categories installed with the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] use separate shared memory, with each performance counter category having its own memory.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-301">Puede especificar el tamaño de memoria compartida independiente mediante la creación de un valor DWORD denominado FileMappingSize en la clave del Registro HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<nombre de categoría >* \ Rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-301">You can specify the size of separate shared memory by creating a DWORD named FileMappingSize in the registry key HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<category name>* \Performance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-302">El valor de FileMappingSize se establece en el tamaño de memoria compartida de la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-302">The FileMappingSize value is set to the shared memory size of the category.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-303">El tamaño predeterminado es decimal 131072.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-303">The default size is 131072 decimal.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-304">Si el valor de FileMappingSize no está presente, el `fileMappingSize` valor del atributo para el `performanceCounters` se utiliza el elemento especificado en el archivo Machine.config, provocando una sobrecarga adicional para el procesamiento del archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-304">If the FileMappingSize value is not present, the `fileMappingSize` attribute value for the `performanceCounters` element specified in the Machine.config file is used, causing additional overhead for configuration file processing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-305">Puede apreciar una mejora del rendimiento de inicio de la aplicación estableciendo el tamaño de asignación de archivo en el registro.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-305">You can realize a performance improvement for application startup by setting the file mapping size in the registry.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-306">Se recomienda encarecidamente que se crean nuevas categorías de contador de rendimiento durante la instalación de la aplicación, no durante la ejecución de la aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-306">It is strongly recommended that new performance counter categories be created during the installation of the application, not during the execution of the application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-307">Esto permite que el tiempo para el sistema operativo actualizar su lista de categorías de contador de rendimiento registrados.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-307">This allows time for the operating system to refresh its list of registered performance counter categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-308">Si no se ha actualizado la lista, se producirá un error al intentar utilizar la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-308">If the list has not been refreshed, the attempt to use the category will fail.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-309">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-309">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-310">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-310">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-311">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-311">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-312">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-312">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-313">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-313">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-314">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-314">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-315">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-315">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-316">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se muestra el uso de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-316">The following code example shows the use of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-317">El ejemplo muestra cómo crear una personalizada, la categoría de contador de rendimiento de varias instancias para el número de pedidos por segundo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-317">The example shows how to create a custom, multi-instance performance counter category for the number of orders per second.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType/CS/program.cs#2)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType/VB/program.vb#2)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-318">A counter name that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is <see langword="null" /> or an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-318">A counter name that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is <see langword="null" /> or an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-319">-or-  A counter that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection already exists.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-319">-or-  A counter that is specified within the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection already exists.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-320">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-320">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-321">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-321">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-322">
            <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-322">
              <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-323">-or-  <paramref name="counterData" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-323">-or-  <paramref name="counterData" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentOutOfRangeException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-324">
            <paramref name="categoryType" /> value is outside of the range of the following values: <see langword="MultiInstance" />, <see langword="SingleInstance" />, or <see langword="Unknown" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-324">
              <paramref name="categoryType" /> value is outside of the range of the following values: <see langword="MultiInstance" />, <see langword="SingleInstance" />, or <see langword="Unknown" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-325">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-325">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-326">-or-  The layout of the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is incorrect for base counters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-326">-or-  The layout of the <paramref name="counterData" /> collection is incorrect for base counters.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-327">A counter of type <see langword="AverageCount64" />, <see langword="AverageTimer32" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimerInverse" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100Ns" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100NsInverse" />, <see langword="RawFraction" />, <see langword="SampleFraction" />, or <see langword="SampleCounter" /> must be immediately followed by one of the base counter types (<see langword="AverageBase" />, <see langword="MultiBase" />, <see langword="RawBase" />, or <see langword="SampleBase" />).</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-327">A counter of type <see langword="AverageCount64" />, <see langword="AverageTimer32" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimerInverse" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100Ns" />, <see langword="CounterMultiTimer100NsInverse" />, <see langword="RawFraction" />, <see langword="SampleFraction" />, or <see langword="SampleCounter" /> must be immediately followed by one of the base counter types (<see langword="AverageBase" />, <see langword="MultiBase" />, <see langword="RawBase" />, or <see langword="SampleBase" />).</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-328">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-328">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-329">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-329">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-330">para realizar tareas administrativas en categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-330">for performing administrative tasks on performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-331">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-331">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Create">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create (string categoryName, string categoryHelp, string counterName, string counterHelp);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create(string categoryName, string categoryHelp, string counterName, string counterHelp) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create(System.String,System.String,System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Create (categoryName As String, categoryHelp As String, counterName As String, counterHelp As String) As PerformanceCounterCategory" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^ Create(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ categoryHelp, System::String ^ counterName, System::String ^ counterHelp);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Create : string * string * string * string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create (categoryName, categoryHelp, counterName, counterHelp)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.Obsolete("Use another overload that uses PerformanceCounterCategoryType instead")</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryHelp" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="counterName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="counterHelp" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-332">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-332">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-333">A description of the custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-333">A description of the custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-334">The name of a new counter, of type <see langword="NumberOfItems32" />, to create as part of the new category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-334">The name of a new counter, of type <see langword="NumberOfItems32" />, to create as part of the new category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-335">A description of the counter that is associated with the new custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-335">A description of the counter that is associated with the new custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-336">Registers a custom performance counter category containing a single counter of type <see langword="NumberOfItems32" /> on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-336">Registers a custom performance counter category containing a single counter of type <see langword="NumberOfItems32" /> on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-337">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new system category, or performance object.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-337">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new system category, or performance object.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-338">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-338">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-339">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-339">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-340">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-340">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-341">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-341">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-342">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-342">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-343">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-343">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-344">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-344">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-345">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y single <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> con texto de ayuda para cada uno, mediante el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%28System.String%2CSystem.String%2CSystem.String%2CSystem.String%29> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-345">The following code example creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and single <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> with help text for each, using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%28System.String%2CSystem.String%2CSystem.String%2CSystem.String%29> method.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfcountercatcreate.cs#2)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatcreate.vb#2)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-346">
            <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" /> or is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-346">
              <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" /> or is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-347">-or-  The counter that is specified by <paramref name="counterName" /> already exists.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-347">-or-  The counter that is specified by <paramref name="counterName" /> already exists.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-348">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-348">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-349">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-349">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-350">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-350">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-351">
            <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-351">
              <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-352">-or-  <paramref name="counterHelp" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-352">-or-  <paramref name="counterHelp" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-353">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-353">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-354">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-354">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-355">para realizar tareas administrativas en categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-355">for performing administrative tasks on performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-356">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-356">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.CounterHelp" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Create">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create (string categoryName, string categoryHelp, System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, string counterName, string counterHelp);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory Create(string categoryName, string categoryHelp, valuetype System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, string counterName, string counterHelp) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create(System.String,System.String,System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType,System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Create (categoryName As String, categoryHelp As String, categoryType As PerformanceCounterCategoryType, counterName As String, counterHelp As String) As PerformanceCounterCategory" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^ Create(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ categoryHelp, System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategoryType categoryType, System::String ^ counterName, System::String ^ counterHelp);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Create : string * string * System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType * string * string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create (categoryName, categoryHelp, categoryType, counterName, counterHelp)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryHelp" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryType" Type="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" />
        <Parameter Name="counterName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="counterHelp" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-357">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-357">The name of the custom performance counter category to create and register with the system.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-358">A description of the custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-358">A description of the custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryType">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-359">One of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" /> values specifying whether the category is <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.MultiInstance" />, <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.SingleInstance" />, or <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.Unknown" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-359">One of the <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType" /> values specifying whether the category is <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.MultiInstance" />, <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.SingleInstance" />, or <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType.Unknown" />.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-360">The name of a new counter to create as part of the new category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-360">The name of a new counter to create as part of the new category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="counterHelp">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-361">A description of the counter that is associated with the new custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-361">A description of the counter that is associated with the new custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-362">Registers the custom performance counter category containing a single counter of type <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterType.NumberOfItems32" /> on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-362">Registers the custom performance counter category containing a single counter of type <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterType.NumberOfItems32" /> on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-363">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new system category, or performance object.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-363">A <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> that is associated with the new system category, or performance object.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-364">El `categoryType` parámetro especifica si la categoría de contador de rendimiento es de instancia única o instancias múltiples.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-364">The `categoryType` parameter specifies whether the performance counter category is single-instance or multi-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-365">De forma predeterminada, una categoría es de instancia única cuando se crea y se convierte en varias instancias cuando se agrega otra instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-365">By default, a category is single-instance when it is created and becomes multi-instance when another instance is added.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-366">Las categorías se crean cuando se configura una aplicación, y se agregan instancias en tiempo de ejecución.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-366">Categories are created when an application is set up, and instances are added at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-367">En las versiones 1.0 y 1.1 de .NET Framework, no es necesario saber si una categoría de contador de rendimiento es de varias instancias o de instancia única.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-367">In the .NET Framework versions 1.0 and 1.1, it is not necessary to know if a performance counter category is multi-instance or single-instance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-368">En el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeración se utiliza para indicar si un contador de rendimiento puede tener varias instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-368">In the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnext](~/includes/dnprdnext-md.md)], the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType> enumeration is used to indicate whether a performance counter can have multiple instances.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-369">Categorías de contador de rendimiento instaladas con el [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] usar memoria compartida independiente, con cada categoría de contador de rendimiento tiene su propia memoria.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-369">Performance counter categories installed with the [!INCLUDE[dnprdnlong](~/includes/dnprdnlong-md.md)] use separate shared memory, with each performance counter category having its own memory.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-370">Puede especificar el tamaño de memoria compartida independiente mediante la creación de un valor DWORD denominado FileMappingSize en la clave del Registro HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<nombre de categoría >* \ Rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-370">You can specify the size of separate shared memory by creating a DWORD named FileMappingSize in the registry key HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\\*\<category name>* \Performance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-371">El valor de FileMappingSize se establece en el tamaño de memoria compartida de la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-371">The FileMappingSize value is set to the shared memory size of the category.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-372">El tamaño predeterminado es decimal 131072.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-372">The default size is 131072 decimal.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-373">Si el valor de FileMappingSize no está presente, el `fileMappingSize` valor del atributo para el `performanceCounters` se utiliza el elemento especificado en el archivo Machine.config, provocando una sobrecarga adicional para el procesamiento del archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-373">If the FileMappingSize value is not present, the `fileMappingSize` attribute value for the `performanceCounters` element specified in the Machine.config file is used, causing additional overhead for configuration file processing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-374">Puede apreciar una mejora del rendimiento de inicio de la aplicación estableciendo el tamaño de asignación de archivo en el registro.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-374">You can realize a performance improvement for application startup by setting the file mapping size in the registry.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-375">Se recomienda encarecidamente que se crean nuevas categorías de contador de rendimiento durante la instalación de la aplicación, no durante la ejecución de la aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-375">It is strongly recommended that new performance counter categories be created during the installation of the application, not during the execution of the application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-376">Esto permite que el tiempo para el sistema operativo actualizar su lista de categorías de contador de rendimiento registrados.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-376">This allows time for the operating system to refresh its list of registered performance counter categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-377">Si no se ha actualizado la lista, se producirá un error al intentar utilizar la categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-377">If the list has not been refreshed, the attempt to use the category will fail.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-378">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-378">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-379">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-379">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-380">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-380">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-381">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-381">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-382">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-382">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-383">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-383">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-384">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-384">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-385">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se muestra el uso de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-385">The following code example shows the use of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-386">El ejemplo muestra cómo crear una categoría de contador de rendimiento personalizado, una sola instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-386">The example shows how to create a custom, single instance performance counter category.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType/CS/program.cs#3)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategoryType/VB/program.vb#3)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-387">
            <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" /> or is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-387">
              <paramref name="counterName" /> is <see langword="null" /> or is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-388">-or-  The counter that is specified by <paramref name="counterName" /> already exists.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-388">-or-  The counter that is specified by <paramref name="counterName" /> already exists.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-389">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-389">-or-  <paramref name="counterName" /> has invalid syntax.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-390">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-390">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-391">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-391">The category already exists on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-392">
            <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-392">
              <paramref name="categoryName" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-393">-or-  <paramref name="counterHelp" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-393">-or-  <paramref name="counterHelp" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-394">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-394">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-395">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-395">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-396">para realizar tareas administrativas en categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-396">for performing administrative tasks on performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-397">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-397">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Delete">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static void Delete (string categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig void Delete(string categoryName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Sub Delete (categoryName As String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static void Delete(System::String ^ categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Delete : string -&gt; unit" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete categoryName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-398">The name of the custom performance counter category to delete.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-398">The name of the custom performance counter category to delete.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-399">Removes the category and its associated counters from the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-399">Removes the category and its associated counters from the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-400">Puede eliminar categorías de contador de rendimiento personalizados solo desde el sistema.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-400">You can delete only custom performance counter categories from the system.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-401">No se puede eliminar un contador de una categoría.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-401">You cannot delete a counter from a category.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-402">Para ello, elimine la categoría y volver a crear la categoría con los contadores que desea conservar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-402">To do so, delete the category and recreate the category with the counters you want to retain.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-403">Para evitar una excepción, confirme que existe la categoría antes de intentar eliminarlo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-403">To avoid an exception, confirm that the category exists before you attempt to delete it.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-404">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-404">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-405">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-405">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-406">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-406">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-407">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-407">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-408">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-408">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-409">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-409">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-410">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-410">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-411">El siguiente ejemplo de código utiliza el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> método para eliminar un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos que contiene.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-411">The following code example uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Delete%2A> method to delete a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects that it contains.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfCounterCatDelete.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatdelete.vb#6)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-412">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-412">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-413">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter has invalid syntax.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-413">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter has invalid syntax.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-414">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-414">It might contain backslash characters ("\\") or have length greater than 80 characters.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-415">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-415">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-416">The category cannot be deleted because it is not a custom category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-416">The category cannot be deleted because it is not a custom category.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-417">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-417">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-418">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-418">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-419">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-419">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Administer" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Create(System.String,System.String,System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection)" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="Exists">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-420">Determines whether the category is registered on the system.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-420">Determines whether the category is registered on the system.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="Exists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool Exists (string categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool Exists(string categoryName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Exists (categoryName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool Exists(System::String ^ categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Exists : string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists categoryName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-421">The name of the performance counter category to look for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-421">The name of the performance counter category to look for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-422">Determines whether the category is registered on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-422">Determines whether the category is registered on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-423">
            <see langword="true" /> if the category is registered; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-423">
              <see langword="true" /> if the category is registered; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-424">El uso de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> método puede provocar una reducción notable del rendimiento mientras se comprueban todos los contadores de rendimiento en el equipo para la disponibilidad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-424">Use of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> method can result in a noticeable performance penalty while all performance counters on the machine are checked for availability.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-425">Si sólo se escriben en un contador de rendimiento, puede evitar la búsqueda global para los contadores de rendimiento mediante la creación del contador de rendimiento cuando se instala la aplicación y suponiendo que la categoría no existe cuando se obtiene acceso al contador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-425">If you are only writing to a performance counter, you can avoid the global search for performance counters by creating the performance counter when the application is installed and assuming the category exists when accessing the counter.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-426">No hay ninguna manera de evitar la búsqueda del contador de rendimiento al leer los contadores de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-426">There is no way to avoid the performance counter search when reading from performance counters.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-427">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-427">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-428">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-428">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-429">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-429">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-430">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-430">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-431">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-431">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-432">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-432">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-433">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-433">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-434">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> existe el objeto denominado "orders".</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-434">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object named "orders" exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-435">Si no, crea el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto utilizando un <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> objeto que contiene dos contadores de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-435">If not, it creates the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object by using a <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> object that contains two performance counters.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CPP/ccd.cpp#1)]
 [!code-csharp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CS/ccd.cs#1)]
 [!code-vb[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/VB/ccd.vb#1)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-436">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-436">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-437">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-437">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-438">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-438">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-439">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-439">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-440">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-440">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-441">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-441">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Exists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool Exists (string categoryName, string machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool Exists(string categoryName, string machineName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function Exists (categoryName As String, machineName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool Exists(System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member Exists : string * string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists (categoryName, machineName)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="machineName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-442">The name of the performance counter category to look for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-442">The name of the performance counter category to look for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="machineName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-443">The name of the computer to examine for the category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-443">The name of the computer to examine for the category.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-444">Determines whether the category is registered on the specified computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-444">Determines whether the category is registered on the specified computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-445">
            <see langword="true" /> if the category is registered; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-445">
              <see langword="true" /> if the category is registered; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-446">El uso de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> método puede provocar una reducción notable del rendimiento mientras se comprueban todos los contadores de rendimiento en el equipo para la disponibilidad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-446">Use of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists%2A> method can result in a noticeable performance penalty while all performance counters on the machine are checked for availability.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-447">Si sólo se escriben en un contador de rendimiento, puede evitar la búsqueda global para los contadores de rendimiento mediante la creación del contador de rendimiento cuando se instala la aplicación y suponiendo que la categoría no existe cuando se obtiene acceso al contador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-447">If you are only writing to a performance counter, you can avoid the global search for performance counters by creating the performance counter when the application is installed and assuming the category exists when accessing the counter.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-448">No hay ninguna manera de evitar la búsqueda del contador de rendimiento al leer los contadores de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-448">There is no way to avoid the performance counter search when reading from performance counters.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-449">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-449">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-450">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-450">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-451">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-451">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-452">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-452">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-453">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-453">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-454">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-454">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-455">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-455">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-456">El ejemplo siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto denominado `Orders` existe.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-456">The following example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object named `Orders` exists.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-457">Si no existe, el ejemplo se crea el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto utilizando un <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> objeto que contiene dos contadores de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-457">If it does not exist, the example creates the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object by using a <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationDataCollection> object that contains two performance counters.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CPP/ccd.cpp#1)]
 [!code-csharp[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/CS/ccd.cs#1)]
 [!code-vb[PerfCounter_ccd#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR/PerfCounter_ccd/VB/ccd.vb#1)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-458">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-458">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-459">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-459">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-460">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-460">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-461">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-461">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.IO.IOException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-462">The network path cannot be found.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-462">The network path cannot be found.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-463">The caller does not have the required permission.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-463">The caller does not have the required permission.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-464">-or-  Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-464">-or-  Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-465">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-465">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-466">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-466">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="GetCategories">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-467">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on a computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-467">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on a computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="GetCategories">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[] GetCategories ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[] GetCategories() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function GetCategories () As PerformanceCounterCategory()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static cli::array &lt;System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^&gt; ^ GetCategories();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member GetCategories : unit -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[]" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories " />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[]</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-468">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-468">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-469">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> objects indicating the categories that are registered on the local computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-469">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> objects indicating the categories that are registered on the local computer.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-470">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-470">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-471">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-471">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-472">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-472">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-473">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-473">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-474">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-474">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-475">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-475">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-476">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-476">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-477">El siguiente ejemplo de código utiliza el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> método para devolver una matriz de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objetos desde el equipo local o en un equipo especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-477">The following code example uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> method to return an array of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objects from the local computer or a specified computer.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-478">Convierte el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> matriz en una matriz de nombres de categoría, que se ordena y se muestra para el usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-478">It converts the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> array into an array of category names, which it sorts and displays for the user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-479">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> sobrecarga se selecciona basándose en si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-479">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> overload is selected based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/cpp/perfcountergetcat.cpp#2)]
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/CS/perfcountergetcat.cs#2)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/VB/perfcountercatgetcat.vb#2)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-480">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-480">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-481">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-481">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-482">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-482">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-483">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-483">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetCategories">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[] GetCategories (string machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[] GetCategories(string machineName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function GetCategories (machineName As String) As PerformanceCounterCategory()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static cli::array &lt;System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounterCategory ^&gt; ^ GetCategories(System::String ^ machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member GetCategories : string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[]" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories machineName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory[]</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="machineName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="machineName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-484">The computer to look on.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-484">The computer to look on.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-485">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on the specified computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-485">Retrieves a list of the performance counter categories that are registered on the specified computer.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-486">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> objects indicating the categories that are registered on the specified computer.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-486">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> objects indicating the categories that are registered on the specified computer.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-487">Para recuperar las categorías en el equipo local, use otra sobrecarga o pasar "." como el `machineName` parámetro.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-487">To retrieve the categories on the local computer, use another overload or pass "." as the `machineName` parameter.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-488">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-488">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-489">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-489">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-490">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-490">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-491">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-491">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-492">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-492">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-493">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-493">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-494">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-494">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-495">El siguiente ejemplo de código utiliza el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> método para devolver una matriz de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objetos desde el equipo local o en un equipo especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-495">The following code example uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> method to return an array of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objects from the local computer or a specified computer.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-496">Convierte el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> matriz en una matriz de nombres de categoría, que se ordena y se muestra para el usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-496">It converts the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> array into an array of category names, which it sorts and displays for the user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-497">El <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> sobrecarga se selecciona basándose en si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-497">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCategories%2A> overload is selected based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/cpp/perfcountergetcat.cpp#2)]
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/CS/perfcountergetcat.cs#2)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/VB/perfcountercatgetcat.vb#2)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-498">The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-498">The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-499">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-499">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-500">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-500">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-501">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-501">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-502">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-502">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="GetCounters">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-503">Retrieves a list of the counters in this performance counter category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-503">Retrieves a list of the counters in this performance counter category.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="GetCounters">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[] GetCounters ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[] GetCounters() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function GetCounters () As PerformanceCounter()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; cli::array &lt;System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounter ^&gt; ^ GetCounters();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.GetCounters : unit -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[]" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.GetCounters " />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[]</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-504">Retrieves a list of the counters in a performance counter category that contains exactly one instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-504">Retrieves a list of the counters in a performance counter category that contains exactly one instance.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-505">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" /> objects indicating the counters that are associated with this single-instance performance counter category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-505">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" /> objects indicating the counters that are associated with this single-instance performance counter category.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-506">Para obtener más información sobre las instancias de objeto de rendimiento, consulte el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> información general de clases.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-506">For more information about performance object instances, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class overview.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-507">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-507">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-508">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-508">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-509">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-509">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-510">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-510">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-511">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-511">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-512">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-512">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-513">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-513">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-514">El ejemplo de código siguiente obtiene una lista de los <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos en un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-514">The following code example gets a list of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects in a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-515">Primero, se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el constructor correspondiente, en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-515">It first creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the appropriate constructor, based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-516">A continuación, usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> método para devolver una matriz de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos, seleccionar la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> sobrecarga en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-516">It then uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> method to return an array of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects, selecting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> overload based on whether an instance name was specified.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-517">Esto <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters> sobrecarga se produce un error a menos que se usa con una categoría de instancia única.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-517">This <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters> overload fails unless it is used with a single-instance category.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/cpp/perfcountercatgetcount.cpp#4)]
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/CS/perfcountercatgetcount.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/VB/perfcountercatgetcount.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-518">The category is not a single instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-518">The category is not a single instance.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-519">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-519">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-520">The category does not have an associated instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-520">The category does not have an associated instance.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-521">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-521">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetCounters">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[] GetCounters (string instanceName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance class System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[] GetCounters(string instanceName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function GetCounters (instanceName As String) As PerformanceCounter()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; cli::array &lt;System::Diagnostics::PerformanceCounter ^&gt; ^ GetCounters(System::String ^ instanceName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.GetCounters : string -&gt; System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[]" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.GetCounters instanceName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter[]</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="instanceName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="instanceName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-522">The performance object instance for which to retrieve the list of associated counters.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-522">The performance object instance for which to retrieve the list of associated counters.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-523">Retrieves a list of the counters in a performance counter category that contains one or more instances.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-523">Retrieves a list of the counters in a performance counter category that contains one or more instances.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-524">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" /> objects indicating the counters that are associated with the specified object instance of this performance counter category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-524">An array of <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" /> objects indicating the counters that are associated with the specified object instance of this performance counter category.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-525">Para representar una categoría de instancia única, pase una cadena vacía ("") para el `instanceName` parámetro.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-525">To represent a single-instance category, pass an empty string ("") for the `instanceName` parameter.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-526">Para obtener más información sobre las instancias de objeto de rendimiento, consulte el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> información general de clases.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-526">For more information about performance object instances, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class overview.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-527">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-527">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-528">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-528">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-529">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-529">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-530">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-530">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-531">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-531">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-532">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-532">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-533">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-533">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-534">El ejemplo de código siguiente obtiene una lista de los <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos en un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-534">The following code example gets a list of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects in a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-535">Primero, se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el constructor correspondiente, en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-535">It first creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the appropriate constructor, based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-536">A continuación, usa el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> método para devolver una matriz de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos, seleccionar la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> sobrecarga en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de instancia.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-536">It then uses the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> method to return an array of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects, selecting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%2A> overload based on whether an instance name was specified.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-537">Esto <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%28System.String%29> sobrecarga se produce un error a menos que se usa con una categoría que contiene las instancias.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-537">This <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetCounters%28System.String%29> overload fails unless it is used with a category that contains instances.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/cpp/perfcountercatgetcount.cpp#4)]
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/CS/perfcountercatgetcount.cs#4)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#4](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/VB/perfcountercatgetcount.vb#4)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-538">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-538">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-539">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property for this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance has not been set.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-539">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property for this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> instance has not been set.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-540">-or-  The category does not contain the instance that is specified by the <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-540">-or-  The category does not contain the instance that is specified by the <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-541">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-541">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-542">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-542">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetInstanceNames">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string[] GetInstanceNames ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance string[] GetInstanceNames() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetInstanceNames" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function GetInstanceNames () As String()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; cli::array &lt;System::String ^&gt; ^ GetInstanceNames();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.GetInstanceNames : unit -&gt; string[]" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.GetInstanceNames " />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String[]</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-543">Retrieves the list of performance object instances that are associated with this category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-543">Retrieves the list of performance object instances that are associated with this category.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-544">An array of strings representing the performance object instance names that are associated with this category or, if the category contains only one performance object instance, a single-entry array that contains an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-544">An array of strings representing the performance object instance names that are associated with this category or, if the category contains only one performance object instance, a single-entry array that contains an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-545">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-545">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-546">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-546">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-547">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-547">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-548">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-548">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-549">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-549">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-550">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-550">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-551">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-551">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-552">El ejemplo de código siguiente obtiene una lista de los <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos en un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-552">The following code example gets a list of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects in a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-553">Primero, se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto utilizando el constructor adecuado en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-553">It first creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object, using the appropriate constructor based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-554">A continuación, usa <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetInstanceNames%2A> para devolver los nombres de instancia como una matriz de <xref:System.String>, que se ordena y se muestra.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-554">It then uses <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetInstanceNames%2A> to return the instance names as an array of <xref:System.String>, which it sorts and displays.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-cpp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#6](~/samples/snippets/cpp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/cpp/perfcountercatgetinst.cpp#6)]
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/CS/perfcountercatgetinst.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.GetMembers/VB/perfcountercatgetinst.vb#6)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-555">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-555">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-556">The property might not have been set.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-556">The property might not have been set.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-557">-or-  The category does not have an associated instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-557">-or-  The category does not have an associated instance.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-558">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-558">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-559">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-559">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.InstanceName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <MemberGroup MemberName="InstanceExists">
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-560">Determines whether the category contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-560">Determines whether the category contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
      </Docs>
    </MemberGroup>
    <Member MemberName="InstanceExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public bool InstanceExists (string instanceName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance bool InstanceExists(string instanceName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function InstanceExists (instanceName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; bool InstanceExists(System::String ^ instanceName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.InstanceExists : string -&gt; bool" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists instanceName" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="instanceName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="instanceName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-561">The performance object instance in this performance counter category to search for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-561">The performance object instance in this performance counter category to search for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-562">Determines whether the specified performance object instance exists in the category that is identified by this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> object's <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-562">Determines whether the specified performance object instance exists in the category that is identified by this <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory" /> object's <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-563">
            <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-563">
              <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-564">Esta sobrecarga de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> no `static`.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-564">This overload of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> is not `static`.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-565">Deberá crear un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto y establecer el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> propiedad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-565">It requires you to create a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object and to set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-566">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-566">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-567">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-567">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-568">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-568">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-569">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-569">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-570">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-570">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-571">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-571">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-572">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-572">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-573">El ejemplo de código siguiente determina si un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instancia existe dentro de un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-573">The following code example determines whether a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instance exists within a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-574">Primero, se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> objeto utilizando el constructor adecuado en función de si se ha especificado un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-574">It first creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> object, using the appropriate constructor based on whether a computer name was specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-575">A continuación, usa <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%28System.String%29> para determinar si la instancia especificada existe y, después, se informa al usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-575">It then uses <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%28System.String%29> to determine whether the specified instance exists, then informs the user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-576">Si no se especifica ningún nombre de instancia, el ejemplo utiliza el nombre de instancia única de forma predeterminada.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-576">If no instance name is specified, the example uses the default single-instance name.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcounterobjinstexists.cs#2)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatobjinstexists.vb#2)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-577">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-577">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-578">The property might not have been set.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-578">The property might not have been set.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-579">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-579">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-580">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-580">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-581">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-581">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-582">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-582">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-583">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-583">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.InstanceName" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="InstanceExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool InstanceExists (string instanceName, string categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool InstanceExists(string instanceName, string categoryName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function InstanceExists (instanceName As String, categoryName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool InstanceExists(System::String ^ instanceName, System::String ^ categoryName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member InstanceExists : string * string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists (instanceName, categoryName)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="instanceName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="instanceName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-584">The performance object instance to search for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-584">The performance object instance to search for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-585">The performance counter category to search.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-585">The performance counter category to search.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-586">Determines whether a specified category on the local computer contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-586">Determines whether a specified category on the local computer contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-587">
            <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-587">
              <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-588">No es posible determinar si existe una instancia de objeto de rendimiento en un equipo sin especificar una categoría específica para buscar en.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-588">It is not possible to determine whether a performance object instance exists on a computer without specifying a specific category to look in.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-589">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-589">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-590">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-590">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-591">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-591">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-592">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-592">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-593">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-593">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-594">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-594">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-595">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-595">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-596">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se utiliza las sobrecargas estáticas de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> para determinar si el dado <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instancia existe en el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-596">The following code example uses the static overloads of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> to determine whether the given <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instance exists in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-597">La sobrecarga se selecciona en función de si se especifica un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-597">The overload is selected based on whether a computer name is specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-598">Si no se especifica ningún nombre de instancia, el ejemplo utiliza el nombre de instancia única de forma predeterminada.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-598">If no instance name is specified, the example uses the default single-instance name.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#10](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcountercatstatinstexists.cs#10)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#10](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatstatinstexists.vb#10)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-599">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-599">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-600">-or-  The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-600">-or-  The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-601">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-601">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-602">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-602">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-603">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-603">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-604">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-604">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-605">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-605">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.InstanceName" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="InstanceExists">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public static bool InstanceExists (string instanceName, string categoryName, string machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public static hidebysig bool InstanceExists(string instanceName, string categoryName, string machineName) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists(System.String,System.String,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Shared Function InstanceExists (instanceName As String, categoryName As String, machineName As String) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; static bool InstanceExists(System::String ^ instanceName, System::String ^ categoryName, System::String ^ machineName);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="static member InstanceExists : string * string * string -&gt; bool" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists (instanceName, categoryName, machineName)" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="instanceName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="categoryName" Type="System.String" />
        <Parameter Name="machineName" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="instanceName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-606">The performance object instance to search for.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-606">The performance object instance to search for.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="categoryName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-607">The performance counter category to search.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-607">The performance counter category to search.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <param name="machineName">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-608">The name of the computer on which to look for the category instance pair.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-608">The name of the computer on which to look for the category instance pair.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-609">Determines whether a specified category on a specified computer contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-609">Determines whether a specified category on a specified computer contains the specified performance object instance.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-610">
            <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-610">
              <see langword="true" /> if the category contains the specified performance object instance; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-611">No es posible determinar si existe una instancia de objeto de rendimiento en un equipo sin especificar una categoría específica para buscar en.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-611">It is not possible to determine whether a performance object instance exists on a computer without specifying a specific category to look in.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-612">Puede utilizar "." para especificar el equipo local.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-612">You can use "." to specify the local computer.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-613">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-613">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-614">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-614">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-615">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-615">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-616">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-616">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-617">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-617">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-618">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-618">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-619">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-619">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-620">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se utiliza las sobrecargas estáticas de <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> para determinar si el dado <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instancia existe en el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-620">The following code example uses the static overloads of <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.InstanceExists%2A> to determine whether the given <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> instance exists in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-621">La sobrecarga se selecciona en función de si se especifica un nombre de equipo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-621">The overload is selected based on whether a computer name is specified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-622">Si no se especifica ningún nombre de instancia, el ejemplo utiliza el nombre de instancia única de forma predeterminada.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-622">If no instance name is specified, the example uses the default single-instance name.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#10](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/CS/perfcountercatstatinstexists.cs#10)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers#10](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ExistMembers/VB/perfcountercatstatinstexists.vb#10)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-623">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-623">The <paramref name="instanceName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-624">-or-  The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-624">-or-  The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-625">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-625">The <paramref name="categoryName" /> parameter is an empty string ("").</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-626">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-626">-or-  The <paramref name="machineName" /> parameter is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-627">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-627">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-628">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-628">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-629">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-629">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-630">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-630">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter.InstanceName" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CounterExists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.Exists(System.String)" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="MachineName">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string MachineName { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string MachineName" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property MachineName As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ MachineName { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.MachineName : string with get, set" Usage="System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-631">Gets or sets the name of the computer on which this category exists.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-631">Gets or sets the name of the computer on which this category exists.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-632">El nombre del equipo en el que existen la categoría de contador de rendimiento y los contadores asociados.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-632">The name of the computer on which the performance counter category and its associated counters exist.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-633">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> con el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor> constructor.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-633">The following code example creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> with the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.%23ctor> constructor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-634">Pide al usuario la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> y los nombres de equipo, a continuación, Establece el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> propiedades de los valores introducidos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-634">It prompts the user for the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> and the computer names, then sets the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A> properties from the entered values.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-635">A continuación, muestra los valores de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, y <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> propiedades o se muestra un mensaje de error si el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> no es accesible.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-635">It then displays the values of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName%2A>, and <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryHelp%2A> properties, or it displays an error message if the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> cannot be accessed.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/CS/perfCounterCatProps.cs#8)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers#8](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.OtherMembers/VB/perfcountercatprops.vb#8)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-636">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> syntax is invalid.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-636">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.MachineName" /> syntax is invalid.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <permission cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermission">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-637">para leer las categorías de contador de rendimiento.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-637">for reading performance counter categories.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-638">Enumeración asociada: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-638">Associated enumeration: <see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterPermissionAccess.Read" />.</span>
          </span>
        </permission>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="ReadCategory">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection ReadCategory ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig instance class System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection ReadCategory() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Function ReadCategory () As InstanceDataCollectionCollection" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; System::Diagnostics::InstanceDataCollectionCollection ^ ReadCategory();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.ReadCategory : unit -&gt; System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection" Usage="performanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory " />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.5000.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>2.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.MonoTODO</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-639">Reads all the counter and performance object instance data that is associated with this performance counter category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-639">Reads all the counter and performance object instance data that is associated with this performance counter category.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-640">An <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection" /> that contains the counter and performance object instance data for the category.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-640">An <see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection" /> that contains the counter and performance object instance data for the category.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-641">Debe establecer el <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> propiedad antes de llamar a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-641">You must set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName%2A> property before you call <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A>.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-642">Leer toda la categoría a la vez puede ser tan eficaz como la lectura de un solo contador debido al modo en que el sistema proporciona los datos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-642">Reading the entire category at once can be as efficient as reading a single counter because of the way that the system provides the data.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-643">Para leer los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition o Windows Server 2003, debe ser miembro del grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento o tener privilegios administrativos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-643">To read performance counters in Windows Vista and later, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, or Windows Server 2003, you must either be a member of the Performance Monitor Users group or have administrative privileges.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-644">Para evitar tener que elevar sus privilegios para tener acceso a los contadores de rendimiento en Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, agréguese al grupo usuarios del Monitor de rendimiento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-644">To avoid having to elevate your privileges to access performance counters in Windows Vista and later, add yourself to the Performance Monitor Users group.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="4f675-645">En Windows Vista y versiones posteriores, el Control de cuentas de usuario (UAC) determina los privilegios de un usuario.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-645">In Windows Vista and later, User Account Control (UAC) determines the privileges of a user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-646">Si es miembro del grupo Administradores integrados, se le asignarán dos símbolos (tokens) de acceso en tiempo de ejecución: un símbolo (token) de acceso de usuario estándar y un símbolo (token) de acceso de administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-646">If you are a member of the Built-in Administrators group, you are assigned two run-time access tokens: a standard user access token and an administrator access token.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-647">De forma predeterminada, se le asignará el rol de usuario estándar.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-647">By default, you are in the standard user role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-648">Para ejecutar el código que tiene acceso a los contadores de rendimiento, primero debe elevar sus privilegios de usuario estándar a administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-648">To execute the code that accesses performance counters, you must first elevate your privileges from standard user to administrator.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-649">Para ello, inicie una aplicación haciendo clic con el botón derecho en el icono de la aplicación e indique que desea ejecutarla como administrador.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-649">You can do this when you start an application by right-clicking the application icon and indicating that you want to run as an administrator.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="4f675-650">En el ejemplo de código siguiente se crea un <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> para un elemento <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> nombre.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-650">The following code example creates a <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> for a specified <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> name.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="4f675-651">A continuación, usa <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A> para devolver un <xref:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection> que contiene los datos de instancia para todas las instancias de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objetos dentro de la <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="4f675-651">It then uses <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.ReadCategory%2A> to return an <xref:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection> that contains instance data for all the instances of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> objects within the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[System.Diagnostics.InstanceData.CopyTo#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.InstanceData.CopyTo/CS/instdatacopyto.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[System.Diagnostics.InstanceData.CopyTo#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_CLR_System/system.Diagnostics.InstanceData.CopyTo/VB/instdatacopyto.vb#6)]  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.InvalidOperationException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-652">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-652">The <see cref="P:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory.CategoryName" /> property is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-653">The property might not have been set.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-653">The property might not have been set.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-654">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-654">A call to an underlying system API failed.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.UnauthorizedAccessException">
          <span data-ttu-id="4f675-655">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="4f675-655">Code that is executing without administrative privileges attempted to read a performance counter.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollectionCollection" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.InstanceDataCollection" />
        <altmember cref="T:System.Diagnostics.InstanceData" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>