<Type Name="ClaimsAuthorizationManager" FullName="System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="fa77fc99c06460c962f41c33b11554f448051d19" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="MT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="es-ES" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="36531915" /></Metadata><TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public class ClaimsAuthorizationManager : System.IdentityModel.Configuration.ICustomIdentityConfiguration" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi beforefieldinit ClaimsAuthorizationManager extends System.Object implements class System.IdentityModel.Configuration.ICustomIdentityConfiguration" />
  <TypeSignature Language="DocId" Value="T:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager" />
  <TypeSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Class ClaimsAuthorizationManager&#xA;Implements ICustomIdentityConfiguration" />
  <TypeSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public ref class ClaimsAuthorizationManager : System::IdentityModel::Configuration::ICustomIdentityConfiguration" />
  <TypeSignature Language="F#" Value="type ClaimsAuthorizationManager = class&#xA;    interface ICustomIdentityConfiguration" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>System.IdentityModel</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>System.Object</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces>
    <Interface>
      <InterfaceName>System.IdentityModel.Configuration.ICustomIdentityConfiguration</InterfaceName>
    </Interface>
  </Interfaces>
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-101">Define la implementación base de un administrador de autorización de notificaciones.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-101">Defines the base implementation for a claims authorization manager.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-102">La <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> clase proporciona la implementación base para un administrador de autorización de notificaciones.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-102">The <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> class provides the base implementation for a claims authorization manager.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-103">Un administrador de autorización de notificaciones puede utilizarse en los dos escenarios siguientes:</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-103">A claims authorization manager can be used in the following two scenarios:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-104">En las aplicaciones basadas en web y servicios, un administrador de autorización de notificaciones puede agregarse a la canalización de procesamiento para proporcionar un punto de extensibilidad de la que puede autorizar el acceso a un recurso de acuerdo con el valor de las notificaciones entrantes antes del código de aplicación que se llama realmente implementa el recurso solicitado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-104">In web-based applications and services, a claims authorization manager  can be added to the processing pipeline to provide an extensibility point from which you can authorize access to a resource according to the value of incoming claims before the application code that actually implements the requested resource is called.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-105">Cuando se usa el <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermission> clase o el <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermissionAttribute> clase declarativo o imperativo de acceso basado en notificaciones comprueba en el código, el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones está configurado para la aplicación es llamado por el sistema para realizar el comprobación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-105">When you use the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermission> class or the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermissionAttribute> class to perform either imperative or declarative claims-based access checks in your code, the claims authorization manager that is configured for your application is called by the system to perform the check.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-106">Comprobaciones de acceso basado en notificaciones se pueden realizar en las aplicaciones basadas en web y aplicaciones de escritorio.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-106">Claims-based access checks can be performed in both web-based applications and desktop applications.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-107">La implementación predeterminada proporcionada por el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> clase autoriza el acceso para cada notificación presentan; sin embargo, puede derivar de esta clase e invalidar el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> método para proporcionar su propia lógica de autorización.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-107">The default implementation provided by the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> class authorizes access for each claim presented; however, you can derive from this class and override the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> method to provide your own authorization logic.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-108">El uso de un administrador de autorización de notificaciones es opcional.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-108">The use of a claims authorization manager is optional.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-109">Puede configurar la aplicación para usar un administrador de autorización de notificaciones mediante programación utilizando la <xref:System.IdentityModel.Configuration.IdentityConfiguration> de clase o de forma declarativa, especificando el [ &lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md)elemento, que es un elemento secundario de la [ &lt;identityConfiguration&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/identityconfiguration.md) elemento en el archivo de configuración de la aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-109">You can configure your application to use a claims authorization manager either programmatically by using the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Configuration.IdentityConfiguration> class or declaratively, by specifying the [&lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) element, which is a child element of the [&lt;identityConfiguration&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/identityconfiguration.md) element in your application configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-110">Si la aplicación es un sitio web o una aplicación web hospedada en Internet Information Services (IIS), debe agregar también el <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule> en la colección de módulos HTTP de ASP.NET.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-110">If your application is a web site or a web application hosted in Internet Information Services (IIS), you must also add the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule> in the ASP.NET HTTP Modules collection.</span></span>  
  
> [!IMPORTANT]
>  <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-111">Cuando se usa el <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermission> clase o el <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermissionAttribute> (clase), el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones que se usa para realizar la comprobación de acceso es lo que se especifica en la configuración de la identidad bajo la <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.FederatedAuthentication.FederationConfiguration%2A?displayProperty=nameWithType> propiedad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-111">When you use the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermission> class or the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsPrincipalPermissionAttribute> class, the claims authorization manager that is used to perform the access check is the one that is specified in the identity configuration under the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.FederatedAuthentication.FederationConfiguration%2A?displayProperty=nameWithType> property.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-112">En un archivo de configuración es la `<identityConfiguration>` sección que se hace referencia desde el valor predeterminado `<federationConfiguration>` elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-112">In a configuration file, it is the `<identityConfiguration>` section that is referenced from the default `<federationConfiguration>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-113">Esto es verdad incluso para servicios Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) y aplicaciones de escritorio.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-113">This is true even for Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) services and desktop applications.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-114">El <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> clase base no toma ninguna configuración adicional; sin embargo, puede invalidar el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> en sus clases derivadas para proporcionar la inicialización de su administrador de autorización de notificaciones de elementos secundarios de la `<claimsAuthorizationElement>`.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-114">The <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> base class does not take any additional configuration; however, you can override the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> in derived classes to provide initialization of your claims authorization manager from child elements of the `<claimsAuthorizationElement>`.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-115">El escenario típico es usar estos elementos secundarios para especificar las directivas de autorización que determinan qué tipos de notificación y los valores son necesarios para obtener acceso a los recursos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-115">The typical scenario is to use these child elements to specify authorization policies which determine which claim types and values are required in order to gain access to which resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-116">Esto no es un requisito de disco duro, aunque es libre para definir cualquier uso y la sintaxis que tenga sentido para su implementación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-116">This is not a hard requirement, though you are free to define whatever usage and syntax make sense for your implementation.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-117">Los ejemplos de código que se usan en el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> temas se toman de la `Claims Based Authorization` ejemplo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-117">The code examples that are used in the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> topics are taken from the `Claims Based Authorization` sample.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-118">Este ejemplo proporciona un administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas que puede autorizar a los sujetos según una directiva que se especifica en configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-118">This sample provides a custom claims authorization manager that can authorize subjects based on a policy that is specified in configuration.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-119">El Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas consta de tres componentes básicos: una clase derivada de <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> que implementa el Administrador de la `ResourceAction` clase que empareja un recurso y una acción y un lector de directiva que lee y compila la directiva de especificada en el archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-119">The custom claims authorization manager consists of three basic components: a class derived from <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> that implements the manager, the `ResourceAction` class that pairs a resource and an action, and a policy reader that reads and compiles policy that is specified in the configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-120">Esto compila la directiva puede, a continuación, usar el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones para evaluar una entidad de seguridad para autorizar el acceso a los recursos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-120">This compiled policy can then be used by the claims authorization manager to evaluate a principal in order to authorize access to resources.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-121">No todos los elementos se muestran por brevedad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-121">Not all elements are shown for the sake of brevity.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-122">Para obtener información acerca de este ejemplo y otros ejemplos disponibles para WIF y dónde descargarlas, consulte [índice de ejemplo de código WIF](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-122">For information about this sample and other samples available for WIF and about where to download them, see [WIF Code Sample Index](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-123">El código siguiente muestra la implementación del Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-123">The following code shows the implementation of the custom claims authorization manager.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-124">El <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> método lee y compila la directiva de configuración mediante el uso de la clase de aplicación auxiliar de lector de directiva (no mostrada) y el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> método concede o deniega el acceso basado en esta directiva.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-124">The <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> method reads and compiles the policy from configuration by using the policy reader helper class (not shown) and the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> method grants or denies access based on this policy.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/myclaimsauthorizationmanager.cs#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-125">El siguiente código muestra la `ResourceAction` clase usada por el Administrador de notificaciones personalizadas.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-125">The following code shows the `ResourceAction` class used by the custom claims manager.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/resourceaction.cs#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-126">El siguiente XML muestra cómo configurar las notificaciones de administrador de autorización que se muestra anteriormente para una aplicación web hospedada en IIS 7.5.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-126">The following XML shows how to configure the claims authorization manager shown above for a web application hosted in IIS 7.5.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-127">Se muestran los elementos específicos de la configuración del Administrador de autorización de notificaciones.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-127">Only the elements specific to the configuration of the claims authorization manager are shown.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-128">Tenga en cuenta que una referencia a la <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule> clase debe agregarse a la canalización en el `<system.Webserver>` elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-128">Note that a reference to the <xref:System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule> class must be added to the pipeline under the `<system.Webserver>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-129">Para sitios y aplicaciones hospedadas en las versiones de IIS anteriores a IIS 7, los módulos se pueden agregar a la canalización en el `<system.Web>` elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-129">For sites and applications hosted in versions of IIS prior to IIS 7 the modules can be added to the pipeline under the `<system.Web>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-130">Esta configuración se muestran pero comentada.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-130">This configuration is shown but commented out.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-131">Se especifica la directiva utilizada por el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizada `<policy>` elementos bajo la [ &lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-131">The policy used by the claims authorization manager is specified by custom `<policy>` elements under the [&lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-132">En la primera directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer una de las notificaciones especificadas con el fin de realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-132">In the first policy, the principal must possess one of the specified claims in order to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-133">En la segunda directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer ambas notificaciones para poder realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-133">In the second policy, the principal must possess both claims to be able to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-134">En todos los demás, la entidad de seguridad se concede automáticamente acceso independientemente de las notificaciones que posee.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-134">In all others, the principal is automatically granted access regardless of the claims it possesses.</span></span>  
  
```  
<configuration>  
  <configSections>  
    <!--WIF 4.5 sections -->  
    <section name="system.identityModel" type="System.IdentityModel.Configuration.SystemIdentityModelSection, System.IdentityModel, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=B77A5C561934E089"/>  
    ...  
  
  </configSections>  
  
  ...  
  
  <system.web>  
    <httpModules>  
      <!--WIF 4.5 modules -->  
      <!--Not needed here for IIS >= 7 -->  
      <!--<add name="ClaimsAuthorizationModule" type="System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule, System.IdentityModel.Services, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089"/>-->  
    </httpModules>  
  </system.web>  
  
  ...  
  
  <system.webServer>  
    <modules>  
      <!--WIF 4.5 modules -->  
      <add name="ClaimsAuthorizationModule" type="System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule, System.IdentityModel.Services, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089"/>  
    </modules>  
  </system.webServer>  
  
  ...  
  
  <!-- WIF 4.5 s.im section-->  
  <system.identityModel>  
    <identityConfiguration>  
      <claimsAuthorizationManager type="ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary.MyClaimsAuthorizationManager, ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary">  
        <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Developers.aspx" action="GET">  
          <or>  
            <claim claimType="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ws/2008/06/identity/claims/role" claimValue="developer" />  
            <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
          </or>  
        </policy>  
        <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Administrators.aspx" action="GET">  
          <and>  
            <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
            <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/ws/2005/05/identity/claims/country" claimValue="USA" />  
          </and>  
        </policy>  
        <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Default.aspx" action="GET">  
        </policy>  
        <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/" action="GET">  
        </policy>  
        <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Claims.aspx" action="GET">  
        </policy>  
      </claimsAuthorizationManager>  
  
      ...  
  
    </identityConfiguration>  
  </system.identityModel>  
  ...  
  
</configuration><configuration>  
  <configSections>  
    <!--WIF 4.5 sections -->  
    <section name="system.identityModel" type="System.IdentityModel.Configuration.SystemIdentityModelSection, System.IdentityModel, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=B77A5C561934E089"/>  
    ...  
  
  </configSections>  
  
  ...  
  
  <system.web>  
    <httpModules>  
      <!--WIF 4.5 modules -->  
      <!--Not needed here for IIS >= 7 -->  
      <!--<add name="ClaimsAuthorizationModule" type="System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule, System.IdentityModel.Services, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089"/>-->  
    </httpModules>  
  </system.web>  
  
  ...  
  
  <system.webServer>  
    <modules>  
      <!--WIF 4.5 modules -->  
      <add name="ClaimsAuthorizationModule" type="System.IdentityModel.Services.ClaimsAuthorizationModule, System.IdentityModel.Services, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089"/>  
    </modules>  
  </system.webServer>  
  
  ...  
  
  <!-- WIF 4.5 s.im section-->  
  <system.identityModel>  
    <identityConfiguration>  
      <claimsAuthorizationManager type="MyClaimsAuthorizationManager.SimpleClaimsAuthoirzationManager, MyClaimsAuthorizationManager" />  
      ...  
  
  </system.identityModel>  
  ...  
  
</configuration>  
```  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public ClaimsAuthorizationManager ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.#ctor" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; ClaimsAuthorizationManager();" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.IdentityModel</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-135">Inicializa una nueva instancia de la clase <see cref="T:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager" />.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-135">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager" /> class.</span></span></summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CheckAccess">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public virtual bool CheckAccess (System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext context);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig newslot virtual instance bool CheckAccess(class System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext context) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess(System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overridable Function CheckAccess (context As AuthorizationContext) As Boolean" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual bool CheckAccess(System::Security::Claims::AuthorizationContext ^ context);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="abstract member CheckAccess : System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext -&gt; bool&#xA;override this.CheckAccess : System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext -&gt; bool" Usage="claimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess context" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.IdentityModel</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="context" Type="System.Security.Claims.AuthorizationContext" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="context"><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-136">El contexto de autorización que contiene el asunto, el recurso y la acción para los que debe comprobarse la autorización.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-136">The authorization context that contains the subject, resource, and action for which authorization is to be checked.</span></span></param>
        <summary><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-137">Cuando se implementa en una clase derivada, comprueba la autorización para el asunto en el contexto especificado para realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-137">When implemented in a derived class, checks authorization for the subject in the specified context to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span></summary>
        <returns><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-138"><see langword="true" /> si el sujeto tiene autorización para realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado; si no, <see langword="false" />.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-138"><see langword="true" /> if the subject is authorized to perform the specified action on the specified resource; otherwise, <see langword="false" />.</span></span></returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-139">La implementación base siempre devuelve `true`, que autoriza el acceso.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-139">The base implementation always returns `true`, which authorizes access.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-140">Puede invalidar este método en una clase derivada para autorizar el acceso según los requisitos de la aplicación de RP.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-140">You can override this method in a derived class to authorize access based on the requirements of your RP application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-141">Si este método devuelve `false`, Windows Identity Foundation (WIF) devuelve un error no autorizado al llamador; de lo contrario, la ejecución se pasa a la aplicación de RP.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-141">If this method returns `false`, Windows Identity Foundation (WIF) returns an unauthorized error to the caller; otherwise, execution is passed to the RP application.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-142">Los ejemplos de código que se usan en el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> temas se toman de la `Claims Based Authorization` ejemplo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-142">The code examples that are used in the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> topics are taken from the `Claims Based Authorization` sample.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-143">Este ejemplo proporciona un administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas que puede autorizar a los sujetos según una directiva que se especifica en configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-143">This sample provides a custom claims authorization manager that can authorize subjects based on a policy that is specified in configuration.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-144">El Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas consta de tres componentes básicos: una clase derivada de <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> que implementa el Administrador de la `ResourceAction` clase que empareja un recurso y una acción y un lector de directiva que lee y compila la directiva de especificada en el archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-144">The custom claims authorization manager consists of three basic components: a class derived from <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> that implements the manager, the `ResourceAction` class that pairs a resource and an action, and a policy reader that reads and compiles policy that is specified in the configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-145">Esto compila la directiva puede, a continuación, usar el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones para evaluar una entidad de seguridad para autorizar el acceso a los recursos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-145">This compiled policy can then be used by the claims authorization manager to evaluate a principal in order to authorize access to resources.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-146">No todos los elementos se muestran por brevedad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-146">Not all elements are shown for the sake of brevity.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-147">Para obtener información acerca de este ejemplo y otros ejemplos disponibles para WIF y dónde descargarlas, consulte [índice de ejemplo de código WIF](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-147">For information about this sample and other samples available for WIF and about where to download them, see [WIF Code Sample Index](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-148">El código siguiente muestra la invalidación de la <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-148">The following code shows the override of the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.CheckAccess%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-149">Este método concede o deniega el acceso basado en una directiva de lectura y se compiló desde el archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-149">This method grants or denies access based on a policy read and compiled from the configuration file.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/myclaimsauthorizationmanager.cs#3)]  
[!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#5](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/myclaimsauthorizationmanager.cs#5)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-150">El siguiente código muestra la `ResourceAction` clase usada por el Administrador de notificaciones personalizadas.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-150">The following code shows the `ResourceAction` class used by the custom claims manager.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/resourceaction.cs#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-151">Se especifica la directiva utilizada por el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizada `<policy>` elementos bajo la [ &lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-151">The policy used by the claims authorization manager is specified by custom `<policy>` elements under the [&lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-152">Esta directiva se lee y compila el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-152">This policy is read and compiled by the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-153">En la primera directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer una de las notificaciones especificadas con el fin de realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-153">In the first policy, the principal must possess one of the specified claims in order to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-154">En la segunda directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer ambas notificaciones para poder realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-154">In the second policy, the principal must possess both claims to be able to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-155">En todos los demás, la entidad de seguridad se concede automáticamente acceso independientemente de las notificaciones que posee.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-155">In all others, the principal is automatically granted access regardless of the claims it possesses.</span></span>  
  
```  
<system.identityModel>  
  <identityConfiguration>  
    <claimsAuthorizationManager type="ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary.MyClaimsAuthorizationManager, ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary">  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Developers.aspx" action="GET">  
        <or>  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ws/2008/06/identity/claims/role" claimValue="developer" />  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
        </or>  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Administrators.aspx" action="GET">  
        <and>  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/ws/2005/05/identity/claims/country" claimValue="USA" />  
        </and>  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Default.aspx" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Claims.aspx" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
    </claimsAuthorizationManager>  
  
    ...  
  
  </identityConfiguration>  
</system.identityModel>  
```  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="LoadCustomConfiguration">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public virtual void LoadCustomConfiguration (System.Xml.XmlNodeList nodelist);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig newslot virtual instance void LoadCustomConfiguration(class System.Xml.XmlNodeList nodelist) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration(System.Xml.XmlNodeList)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overridable Sub LoadCustomConfiguration (nodelist As XmlNodeList)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual void LoadCustomConfiguration(System::Xml::XmlNodeList ^ nodelist);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="abstract member LoadCustomConfiguration : System.Xml.XmlNodeList -&gt; unit&#xA;override this.LoadCustomConfiguration : System.Xml.XmlNodeList -&gt; unit" Usage="claimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration nodelist" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <Implements>
        <InterfaceMember>M:System.IdentityModel.Configuration.ICustomIdentityConfiguration.LoadCustomConfiguration(System.Xml.XmlNodeList)</InterfaceMember>
      </Implements>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.IdentityModel</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="nodelist" Type="System.Xml.XmlNodeList" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="nodelist"><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-156">Elementos de configuración personalizados.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-156">The custom configuration elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-157">Todos los nodos de la lista son de tipo <see cref="T:System.Xml.XmlElement" />.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-157">Each node in the list is of type <see cref="T:System.Xml.XmlElement" />.</span></span></param>
        <summary><span data-ttu-id="7c89a-158">Cuando se reemplaza en una clase derivada, carga la configuración personalizada de XML.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-158">When overridden in a derived class, loads custom configuration from XML.</span></span></summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-159">El <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthenticationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> se llama al método mediante la infraestructura de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-159">The <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthenticationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> method is called by the configuration infrastructure.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-160">Cuando se llama a este método, el `nodelist` contendrá los elementos secundarios de nivel superior de la [ &lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) elemento desde el archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-160">When this method is called, the `nodelist` will contain the top-level child elements of the [&lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) element from the configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-161">A su vez, cada uno de estos elementos podría contener atributos o elementos secundarios según el esquema de configuración que define para la clase derivada.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-161">Each of these elements may, in turn, contain attributes or child elements depending on the configuration schema you define for your derived class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-162">Si no hay elementos secundarios aparecen bajo el `<claimsAuthorizationManager>` elemento en el archivo de configuración, no se llama a este método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-162">If no child elements appear under the `<claimsAuthorizationManager>` element in the configuration file, this method is not called.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-163">La implementación predeterminada inicia un <xref:System.NotImplementedException>.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-163">The default implementation throws a <xref:System.NotImplementedException>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-164">Invalide este método en una clase derivada para habilitar la inicialización de su administrador de autorización de notificaciones desde un archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-164">Override this method in your derived class to enable initialization of your claims authorization manager from a configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-165">Normalmente, los elementos de configuración se usan para expresar una directiva de autorización; Sin embargo, puede definir los elementos y usarlos en cualquier modo que tenga sentido según los requisitos de la aplicación.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-165">Typically, the configuration elements are used to express an authorization policy; however, you can define elements and use them in any way that makes sense based on the requirements of your application.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-166">Los ejemplos de código que se usan en el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> temas se toman de la `Claims Based Authorization` ejemplo.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-166">The code examples that are used in the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> topics are taken from the `Claims Based Authorization` sample.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-167">Este ejemplo proporciona un administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas que puede autorizar a los sujetos según una directiva que se especifica en configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-167">This sample provides a custom claims authorization manager that can authorize subjects based on a policy that is specified in configuration.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-168">El Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizadas consta de tres componentes básicos: una clase derivada de <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> que implementa el Administrador de la `ResourceAction` clase que empareja un recurso y una acción y un lector de directiva que lee y compila la directiva de especificada en el archivo de configuración.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-168">The custom claims authorization manager consists of three basic components: a class derived from <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager> that implements the manager, the `ResourceAction` class that pairs a resource and an action, and a policy reader that reads and compiles policy that is specified in the configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-169">Esto compila la directiva puede, a continuación, usar el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones para evaluar una entidad de seguridad para autorizar el acceso a los recursos.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-169">This compiled policy can then be used by the claims authorization manager to evaluate a principal in order to authorize access to resources.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-170">No todos los elementos se muestran por brevedad.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-170">Not all elements are shown for the sake of brevity.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-171">Para obtener información acerca de este ejemplo y otros ejemplos disponibles para WIF y dónde descargarlas, consulte [índice de ejemplo de código WIF](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-171">For information about this sample and other samples available for WIF and about where to download them, see [WIF Code Sample Index](~/docs/framework/security/wif-code-sample-index.md).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-172">El código siguiente muestra la invalidación de la <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-172">The following code shows the override of the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-173">Este método usa una clase de lector de directiva de aplicación auxiliar (no mostrada) para leer y compilar especificadas en el archivo de configuración de directivas de autorización.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-173">This method uses a helper policy reader class (not shown) to read and compile authorization policies specified in the configuration file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-174">Las directivas se agregan a un diccionario y son accesibles por un `ResourceAction` objeto de clave que se crea a partir de la acción y recursos para los que están destinados.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-174">Policies are added to a dictionary and are accessed by a `ResourceAction` key object that is created from the resource and action for which they are intended.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/myclaimsauthorizationmanager.cs#3)]  
[!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#4](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/myclaimsauthorizationmanager.cs#4)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-175">El siguiente código muestra la `ResourceAction` clase usada por el Administrador de notificaciones personalizadas.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-175">The following code shows the `ResourceAction` class used by the custom claims manager.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WifClaimsBasedAuthorization#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_Misc/wifclaimsbasedauthorization/cs/claimsauthorizationlibrary/resourceaction.cs#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-176">Se especifica la directiva utilizada por el Administrador de autorización de notificaciones personalizada `<policy>` elementos bajo la [ &lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt; ](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) elemento.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-176">The policy used by the claims authorization manager is specified by custom `<policy>` elements under the [&lt;claimsAuthorizationManager&gt;](~/docs/framework/configure-apps/file-schema/windows-identity-foundation/claimsauthorizationmanager.md) element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-177">Esta directiva se lee y compila el <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> método.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-177">This policy is read and compiled by the <xref:System.Security.Claims.ClaimsAuthorizationManager.LoadCustomConfiguration%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-178">En la primera directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer una de las notificaciones especificadas con el fin de realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-178">In the first policy, the principal must possess one of the specified claims in order to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-179">En la segunda directiva, la entidad de seguridad debe poseer ambas notificaciones para poder realizar la acción especificada en el recurso especificado.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-179">In the second policy, the principal must possess both claims to be able to perform the specified action on the specified resource.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7c89a-180">En todos los demás, la entidad de seguridad se concede automáticamente acceso independientemente de las notificaciones que posee.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7c89a-180">In all others, the principal is automatically granted access regardless of the claims it possesses.</span></span>  
  
```  
<system.identityModel>  
  <identityConfiguration>  
    <claimsAuthorizationManager type="ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary.MyClaimsAuthorizationManager, ClaimsAuthorizationLibrary">  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Developers.aspx" action="GET">  
        <or>  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ws/2008/06/identity/claims/role" claimValue="developer" />  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
        </or>  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Administrators.aspx" action="GET">  
        <and>  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/claims/Group" claimValue="Administrator" />  
          <claim claimType="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/ws/2005/05/identity/claims/country" claimValue="USA" />  
        </and>  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Default.aspx" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
      <policy resource="http://localhost:28491/Claims.aspx" action="GET">  
      </policy>  
    </claimsAuthorizationManager>  
  
    ...  
  
  </identityConfiguration>  
</system.identityModel>  
```  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>